<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Farady Electric</title>
    <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Farady Electric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 13:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.farady-electric.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Auto Recloser</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/auto-recloser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:36:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/auto-recloser/</guid>
      <description>General Farady Electric strives to bring our customers the latest technology and competitive pricing and best service for pole mounted Auto circuit recloser
The FAR series Auto circuit recloser can use on overhead distribution lines as well as distribution substation applications for all voltage classes 11kV up to 38kV at 50/60HZ power system. And its rated current can reach 1600A.
The FAR series Auto circuit recloser integrates the functions of control, protection, measurement,communication,fault detection,on-line monitoring of closing or opening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gas insulated load break switch</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/gas-insulated-load-break-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:45:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/gas-insulated-load-break-switch/</guid>
      <description>General LW3F type pole-install load switch was used in 12kV,24kV,33kV rated voltage, rated current 400/630A; 50/60HZ with the load current; over load current of power line open circuit and opening and closing electric systems.The switch can equiped with a conttoller with most advanced technical parameter.
LW3FA type LW3F is manaully LBS for choice.
LW3FM type LW3F is a intelligent type LBS for choice. It can automatically disconnect when the distribution line was break down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onload disconnector switch</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/onload-disconnector-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:43:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/onload-disconnector-switch/</guid>
      <description>General RTS type Outdoor on load break switch (switch disconnector) contained in this list are destined to switch stub lines and ring main lines or transformers( It can be equipped with MV HRC fuse links as short circuit protection function) or for switching under on load conditions.
RTS type switch comply with IEC/IEEE and DVE-recommendation standards. Especially comply with DIN VDE 0670 part 3 and IEC publication IEC-60265, IEC-129.
Service Environment a) Air temperature: Maximum temperature: +75℃; Minimum temperature:-45℃</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCS Capacitor Switch</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/fcs-capacitor-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:42:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/fcs-capacitor-switch/</guid>
      <description>General The Farady’s new generation FCS capacitor switch is a long mechnical life design vacuum switch that provides an operational life of over 100,000 (30,000open/close) maintenance-free operations.
Using the FCS will result in substantial savings from reduced maintenance and maximized bank uptime and will also improve Power Quality.
The FCS all comply with relative standard ANSI C37.66/IEC60071
Service condition Ambient temperature: -40℃~+85℃, day temperature difference: 25℃；
Altitude:Below 2000m(special condition pls contact Farady Technical);</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SF6 GAS RMU</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/sf6-gas-rmu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:29:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/sf6-gas-rmu/</guid>
      <description>Standard instruction Gerneral FGRMU is a SF6 gas insulated switchgear ring main unit for the secondary distribution network. FGRMU can be supplied in 10 different configurations suitable for most switching applications in 12/24/36 kV distribution networks. It is have Non-extension and extension able modular compact switchgear, they represent a complete solution for 12/24/36 kV secondary distribution networks. FGRMU and FGRMU-plus have identical user interfaces. FGRMU is a completely sealed system with a stainless-steel tank containing all live parts and switching functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solid Insulation Ring Main Unit</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/solid-insulation-ring-main-unit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:28:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/solid-insulation-ring-main-unit/</guid>
      <description>General Solid Insulated ring main unit is a RMU which uses solid insulated materials as main insulating medium.
Connect the vacuum arc-extinguishing chamber with its electric conduction, disconnector, earthing switches, main bus, branch main bus and other dominant electric circuits.
After single or combination, cover it with insulated solid medium as one or multiple functional, recombinational or re-extensible models with full insulation or full airtightness. The touchable model surface is coated with a conductive or semi-conductive shielding layer which can be directly and solidly grounded to the ring main unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MNS LV switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mns-lv-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:17:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mns-lv-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>General MNS LV withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as device) is manufactured by standard module through consulting MNS series low voltage switch cabinet of Switzerland ABB Company, and synthetically improved. The device is applicable to the system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 660V and below, used as control device for various power generation, transmission, distribution, power transfer and power consumption device. It is widely used in low voltage distribution system of various mining enterprise, tall building and hotel, municipal construction etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>33kV metal clad switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/33kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:14:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/33kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>General KYN61-36 air-insulated metal-clad withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter as switchgear is a kind of MV switchgear.
It is designed as a withdrawable module type panel, and the withdrawable part is fitted with VD4-36E,VD4-36 withdrawable vacuum circuit breaker manufactured by FARADY Electric Company . It can also be fitted with isolation truck, PT truck, fuses truck and so on. It is applicable to three phase AC 50/60 Hz power system,and mainly used for the transmission and distribution of electrical power and control,protection,monitoring of the circuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12/24KV Metal Clad Switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/12-24kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:07:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/12-24kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>General KYN28 indoor metal-clad withdrawable switchgear(hereinafter short as switchgear)is a complete power distribution device for 3.6~24kV,3-phase AC 50Hz,single-bus and single-bus sectionalized system.　It is mainly used for power transmission of middle/small generators in power plants;　power receiving,　transmission for substations in power distribution and power system of factories, mines and enterprises,　and starting of large high-voltage motor,　etc.,so as to control,　protect and monitor the system.　The switchgear meets IEC298,GB3906-91.In addition to be used with domestic VS1 vacuum circuit breaker,　it can also be used with VD4 from ABB,3AH5 from Siemens domestic ZN65A,and VB2 from GE,　etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor LV Distribution Box</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/outdoor-lv-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:32:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/outdoor-lv-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>General With the strong assistance of our adept professionals, we are engrossed in supplying a large variety of Feeder Pillar Panel. The offered panel is Integrated with power distribution/metering/protection/control/reactive power compensation function. This panel is extensively used in commercial and residential sectors for low voltage distribution applications. Before offering to the clients, this panel is stringently tested in order to ensure its flawless performance. Comply with standard IEC 60439
Service Environment a) Air temperature: Maximum temperature: +40℃; Minimum temperature:-25℃</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VB4 Series Vacuum Circuit Breaker</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/vb4-series-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:48:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/vb4-series-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>General VB4P medium-voltage indoor vacuum circuit breaker is applicable for three-phase AC power system of rated voltage up to 12~24kV and frequency 50/60Hz,widely used in many fields such as power plant, transformer substation, petrol chemical industry, metallurgy, manufacturing industry, airport, residential area, etc., to control and protect the electric equipment, especially, It is used for the occasion that needs infrequent operation at rated current or multi-breaking short circuit current, may be mounted in the indoor air insulating switchgear like type KYN28 or AMS, ABB type ZS1 series, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Oil Immersed Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-oil-immersed-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 13:59:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-oil-immersed-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General Farady offers a complete range of distribution transformers designed to grant the reliability, durability, and efficiency required in utility, industrial, and commercial applications. Farady’s liquid-filled transformers are manufactured in accordance with the most demanding industry and international standards. Compliance with important standards, from IEC to VDE, is a matter of course, just as much as the exclusive use of high-quality materials. Qualified employees implement the demanding standards in daily practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dry Type Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/dry-type-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:54:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/dry-type-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General Farady Electric manufacture a complete range of three phase distribution transformers, including oil-immersed type &amp;amp; cast resin dry-type transformer, we always designed with increased margins of safety and reliablity,and meet the IEC60076, IEEE Std
Three phase resin-cast dry-type distribution transformer is with features of low loss, compact and light weight, low noise level,clamp-proof,anti-fouling,high mechanical strength, flame resisting, strong overload ability and low partial discharge quality,they are application to power transmission and distribution system,hotel,restaurant,commercial building,stadiums,chemical plants,stations,aiports,offshore drilling platforms,especially to heavy load centers and places with special fire protection requirements</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Pad Mounted Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-pad-mounted-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:52:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-pad-mounted-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General Farady Electric is an ISO9001-2008 certified company that has been manufacturing exceptional distribution and power transformer for last 10 years, one of the reasons for our success over the last decade has been a rigid quality system supported by our quality assurance programs and ongoing research and development, all design undergo complete type testing and routine testing, as per the applicable standards Farady Electric&amp;rsquo;s three phase pad mounted distribution transformers provide a reliable and affordable solution for clients who need to reduce their overall operating costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amorphous Alloy Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/amorphous-alloy-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:50:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/amorphous-alloy-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General An amorphous metal transformer (AMT) is a type of energy efficient transformer found on electric grids. The magnetic core of this transformer is made with a ferromagnetic amorphous metal. The typical material (Metglas) is an alloy of iron with boron, silicon, and phosphorus in the form of thin (e.g. 25 µm) foils. These materials have high magnetic susceptibility, very low co ercivity and high electrical resistance. The high resistance and thin foils lead to low losses by eddy currents when subjected to alternating magnetic fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kiosk Compact Substation</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/kiosk-compact-substation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:56:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/kiosk-compact-substation/</guid>
      <description>General YBW series prefabricated compact transformer is a kind of set of equipment which assembles the MV switch apparatus, prefabricated compact transformer, LV distribution equipment together according to fixed connection scheme. This series substation is suitable for neighborhood unit, hotel, large-scale work site and high building that the voltage is 11kV /15kV/17.5kV/34.5kV prefabricated compact transformer, the frequency is 50/60Hz and the prefabricated compact transformer capacity is under 2500kVA Standards: IEC60076,IEC1330, ANSI/IEEE C57.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single Phase Pole Mounted Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/single-phase-pole-mounted-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:58:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/single-phase-pole-mounted-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General Farady overhead transformer may be used alone for the supply of a single phase load or as one of three units in a bank for the supply of a three phase load. The unit may be direct mounted to a wooden or concrete pole, or cluster mounted on a pole for three phase use. Our single phase overhead distribution transformer is commonly used in various places including rural areas, remote regions and scattered villages to provide high quality power supply for daily lighting, agricultural production and industrial plants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor Metering Units</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/outdoor-metering-units/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:10:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/outdoor-metering-units/</guid>
      <description>General OMU series three phase oil-immersed metering units (hereinafter referred to as metering unit) applies to the rated voltage of 11kV and 33kV,rated frequency of 50-60Hz for power measurement with the three phase three wire and three phase four wire AC network, by the combination of CT/PT together. This product meet the std IEC61869-1.2&amp;amp;3
Service condition l Ambient temperature: -40ºC~+85ºC, day temperature difference: 25ºC;
l Altitude:≤3000m area;
l Wind speed no exceeds 35m/s;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single Phase Automatic Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/single-phase-automatic-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:34:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/single-phase-automatic-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description>General Farady Electric VR-8 voltage regulators are designed for reliable operation and ease of mainte-nance and are supplied with a full array of standard features for routine applications. Optional accessories are available to ac-commodate special applicate it is also suitable for the energy saving projects for railway and urban grid. Farady Electric series voltage regulators are available with a full comply with of standard IEEE C57.15 &amp;amp; IEC 60076-21
Standard Features • Tap changer with motor and power supply</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Step Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-step-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:33:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-step-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description>General Variation of voltage can have detrimental effects on Utilities and their customers. To prevent customer complaints, loss of revenue due to sub-normal voltage, and increased costs due to higher line losses, FARADY has designed the TVR Voltage Regulator with you, “The Utilities”, in mind. With over 10 years of experience, FARADY has designed the most reliable regulator ever assembled.
Ideally the distribution lines should to be able to keep the whole line of constant voltage, but in actual , the impedance of the distribution line will result in that the voltage of end and terminal is no the same .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Var Compensator (SVC)</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/static-var-compensator-svc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:58:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/static-var-compensator-svc/</guid>
      <description>General Farady FDWK type line reactive power automatic compensation series device is used for 6kV~33kV lines. It uses microcomputer technology &amp;amp; Vacuum contactor t o automatic control by switching on &amp;amp; off shunt capacitor banks according to the parameters of voltage, time, power factor and reactive power to improve line power factor, reduce line consumption and improve voltage quality.
Product standard IEC 60871-1 - Shunt capacitors for a.c. power systems having a rated voltage above 1 000 V – Part 1: General</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morocoo ONEE Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/morocoo-onee-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:59:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/morocoo-onee-regulator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MALAWI MAREP</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/malawi-marep/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:58:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/malawi-marep/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China National State Grid</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/china-national-state-grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:57:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/china-national-state-grid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECG 20MVA mobile AVR(Ghana)</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/ecg-20mva-mobile-avrghana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:56:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/ecg-20mva-mobile-avrghana/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethiopia EEU transfomrer</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/ethiopia-eeu-transfomrer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:55:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/ethiopia-eeu-transfomrer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAKISTAN Karachi seaport phase 3</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/pakistan-karachi-seaport-phase-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:54:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/pakistan-karachi-seaport-phase-3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afghanistan Breshna Shirkat(DABS)</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/afghanistan-breshna-shirkatdabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:53:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/afghanistan-breshna-shirkatdabs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mongolia Recolser </title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mongolia-recolser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:48:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mongolia-recolser/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMAN MAJAN ELECTRICITY </title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/oman-majan-electricity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:48:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/oman-majan-electricity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rwanda EDCL</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/rwanda-edcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:48:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/rwanda-edcl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanzania TANESCO </title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/tanzania-tanesco/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:48:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/tanzania-tanesco/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Middle east electricity （MEE） dubai</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/middle-east-electricity-mee-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:41:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/middle-east-electricity-mee-dubai/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>farady in IEEE PES T&amp;D Dallas</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/farady-in-ieee-pes-td-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:40:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/farady-in-ieee-pes-td-dallas/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STEP VOLTAGE REGULATOR RUNNING IN COTE D’VOTE CIE</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/step-voltage-regulator-running-in-cote-dvote-cie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:37:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/step-voltage-regulator-running-in-cote-dvote-cie/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Bangladesh 2016 Int’l Expo.</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/farady-in-18th-power-bangladesh-2016-intl-expo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/farady-in-18th-power-bangladesh-2016-intl-expo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PAKISTAN Karachi seaport Phase 3</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/pakistan-karachi-seaport-phase-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:54:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/pakistan-karachi-seaport-phase-3/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IIEE 3E XPO</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/iiee-3e-xpo-at-the-smx-convention-center-mall-of-asia-pasay-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:32:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/iiee-3e-xpo-at-the-smx-convention-center-mall-of-asia-pasay-city/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan commission &amp; installation</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/pakistan-commission-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:29:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/pakistan-commission-installation/</guid>
      <description>Excellent job！Successfully Voltage regulator project in PMI SAHIWAL Pakistan with our experienced engineer and local technical teams’s commission &amp;amp; installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mee Middle East Electricity 2018 Exhibition Dubai</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mee-middle-east-electricity-2018-exhibition-dubai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:27:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mee-middle-east-electricity-2018-exhibition-dubai/</guid>
      <description>Farady will be present at the 2018 MEE exhibition. Come and visit us at our booth #H1.C19.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farady Information Exchanging Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/farady-information-exchanging-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:23:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/farady-information-exchanging-conference/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
