<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RMU &amp; Switchgear on Farady Electric</title>
    <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/category/switchgear/</link>
    <description>Recent content in RMU &amp; Switchgear on Farady Electric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:12:27 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.farady-electric.com/category/switchgear/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SF6 GAS RMU</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/sf6-gas-rmu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:29:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/sf6-gas-rmu/</guid>
      <description>Standard instruction Gerneral FGRMU is a SF6 gas insulated switchgear ring main unit for the secondary distribution network. FGRMU can be supplied in 10 different configurations suitable for most switching applications in 12/24/36 kV distribution networks. It is have Non-extension and extension able modular compact switchgear, they represent a complete solution for 12/24/36 kV secondary distribution networks. FGRMU and FGRMU-plus have identical user interfaces. FGRMU is a completely sealed system with a stainless-steel tank containing all live parts and switching functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solid Insulation Ring Main Unit</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/solid-insulation-ring-main-unit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:28:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/solid-insulation-ring-main-unit/</guid>
      <description>General Solid Insulated ring main unit is a RMU which uses solid insulated materials as main insulating medium.
Connect the vacuum arc-extinguishing chamber with its electric conduction, disconnector, earthing switches, main bus, branch main bus and other dominant electric circuits.
After single or combination, cover it with insulated solid medium as one or multiple functional, recombinational or re-extensible models with full insulation or full airtightness. The touchable model surface is coated with a conductive or semi-conductive shielding layer which can be directly and solidly grounded to the ring main unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MNS LV switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mns-lv-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:17:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/mns-lv-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>General MNS LV withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter referred to as device) is manufactured by standard module through consulting MNS series low voltage switch cabinet of Switzerland ABB Company, and synthetically improved. The device is applicable to the system with AC 50Hz, rated working voltage 660V and below, used as control device for various power generation, transmission, distribution, power transfer and power consumption device. It is widely used in low voltage distribution system of various mining enterprise, tall building and hotel, municipal construction etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>33kV metal clad switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/33kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:14:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/33kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>General KYN61-36 air-insulated metal-clad withdrawable switchgear (hereinafter as switchgear is a kind of MV switchgear.
It is designed as a withdrawable module type panel, and the withdrawable part is fitted with VD4-36E,VD4-36 withdrawable vacuum circuit breaker manufactured by FARADY Electric Company . It can also be fitted with isolation truck, PT truck, fuses truck and so on. It is applicable to three phase AC 50/60 Hz power system,and mainly used for the transmission and distribution of electrical power and control,protection,monitoring of the circuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12/24KV Metal Clad Switchgear</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/12-24kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:07:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/12-24kv-metal-clad-switchgear/</guid>
      <description>General KYN28 indoor metal-clad withdrawable switchgear(hereinafter short as switchgear)is a complete power distribution device for 3.6~24kV,3-phase AC 50Hz,single-bus and single-bus sectionalized system.　It is mainly used for power transmission of middle/small generators in power plants;　power receiving,　transmission for substations in power distribution and power system of factories, mines and enterprises,　and starting of large high-voltage motor,　etc.,so as to control,　protect and monitor the system.　The switchgear meets IEC298,GB3906-91.In addition to be used with domestic VS1 vacuum circuit breaker,　it can also be used with VD4 from ABB,3AH5 from Siemens domestic ZN65A,and VB2 from GE,　etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor LV Distribution Box</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/outdoor-lv-distribution-box/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:32:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/outdoor-lv-distribution-box/</guid>
      <description>General With the strong assistance of our adept professionals, we are engrossed in supplying a large variety of Feeder Pillar Panel. The offered panel is Integrated with power distribution/metering/protection/control/reactive power compensation function. This panel is extensively used in commercial and residential sectors for low voltage distribution applications. Before offering to the clients, this panel is stringently tested in order to ensure its flawless performance. Comply with standard IEC 60439
Service Environment a) Air temperature: Maximum temperature: +40℃; Minimum temperature:-25℃</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VB4 Series Vacuum Circuit Breaker</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/vb4-series-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:48:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/vb4-series-vacuum-circuit-breaker/</guid>
      <description>General VB4P medium-voltage indoor vacuum circuit breaker is applicable for three-phase AC power system of rated voltage up to 12~24kV and frequency 50/60Hz,widely used in many fields such as power plant, transformer substation, petrol chemical industry, metallurgy, manufacturing industry, airport, residential area, etc., to control and protect the electric equipment, especially, It is used for the occasion that needs infrequent operation at rated current or multi-breaking short circuit current, may be mounted in the indoor air insulating switchgear like type KYN28 or AMS, ABB type ZS1 series, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
