<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Auto Recloser&amp;LBS on Farady Electric</title>
    <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/category/auto-recloser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Auto Recloser&amp;LBS on Farady Electric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:14:34 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.farady-electric.com/category/auto-recloser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Auto Recloser</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/auto-recloser/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:36:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/auto-recloser/</guid>
      <description>General Farady Electric strives to bring our customers the latest technology and competitive pricing and best service for pole mounted Auto circuit recloser
The FAR series Auto circuit recloser can use on overhead distribution lines as well as distribution substation applications for all voltage classes 11kV up to 38kV at 50/60HZ power system. And its rated current can reach 1600A.
The FAR series Auto circuit recloser integrates the functions of control, protection, measurement,communication,fault detection,on-line monitoring of closing or opening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gas insulated load break switch</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/gas-insulated-load-break-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:45:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/gas-insulated-load-break-switch/</guid>
      <description>General LW3F type pole-install load switch was used in 12kV,24kV,33kV rated voltage, rated current 400/630A; 50/60HZ with the load current; over load current of power line open circuit and opening and closing electric systems.The switch can equiped with a conttoller with most advanced technical parameter.
LW3FA type LW3F is manaully LBS for choice.
LW3FM type LW3F is a intelligent type LBS for choice. It can automatically disconnect when the distribution line was break down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onload disconnector switch</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/onload-disconnector-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:43:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/onload-disconnector-switch/</guid>
      <description>General RTS type Outdoor on load break switch (switch disconnector) contained in this list are destined to switch stub lines and ring main lines or transformers( It can be equipped with MV HRC fuse links as short circuit protection function) or for switching under on load conditions.
RTS type switch comply with IEC/IEEE and DVE-recommendation standards. Especially comply with DIN VDE 0670 part 3 and IEC publication IEC-60265, IEC-129.
Service Environment a) Air temperature: Maximum temperature: +75℃; Minimum temperature:-45℃</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FCS Capacitor Switch</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/fcs-capacitor-switch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:42:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/fcs-capacitor-switch/</guid>
      <description>General The Farady’s new generation FCS capacitor switch is a long mechnical life design vacuum switch that provides an operational life of over 100,000 (30,000open/close) maintenance-free operations.
Using the FCS will result in substantial savings from reduced maintenance and maximized bank uptime and will also improve Power Quality.
The FCS all comply with relative standard ANSI C37.66/IEC60071
Service condition Ambient temperature: -40℃~+85℃, day temperature difference: 25℃；
Altitude:Below 2000m(special condition pls contact Farady Technical);</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
