<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulator&amp;Power Quality on Farady Electric</title>
    <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/category/power-quality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulator&amp;Power Quality on Farady Electric</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:16:45 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.farady-electric.com/category/power-quality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Single Phase Automatic Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/single-phase-automatic-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:34:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/single-phase-automatic-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description>General Farady Electric VR-8 voltage regulators are designed for reliable operation and ease of mainte-nance and are supplied with a full array of standard features for routine applications. Optional accessories are available to ac-commodate special applicate it is also suitable for the energy saving projects for railway and urban grid. Farady Electric series voltage regulators are available with a full comply with of standard IEEE C57.15 &amp;amp; IEC 60076-21
Standard Features • Tap changer with motor and power supply</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Step Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-step-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:33:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/three-phase-step-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description>General Variation of voltage can have detrimental effects on Utilities and their customers. To prevent customer complaints, loss of revenue due to sub-normal voltage, and increased costs due to higher line losses, FARADY has designed the TVR Voltage Regulator with you, “The Utilities”, in mind. With over 10 years of experience, FARADY has designed the most reliable regulator ever assembled.
Ideally the distribution lines should to be able to keep the whole line of constant voltage, but in actual , the impedance of the distribution line will result in that the voltage of end and terminal is no the same .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static Var Compensator (SVC)</title>
      <link>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/static-var-compensator-svc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 09:58:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.farady-electric.com/post/static-var-compensator-svc/</guid>
      <description>General Farady FDWK type line reactive power automatic compensation series device is used for 6kV~33kV lines. It uses microcomputer technology &amp;amp; Vacuum contactor t o automatic control by switching on &amp;amp; off shunt capacitor banks according to the parameters of voltage, time, power factor and reactive power to improve line power factor, reduce line consumption and improve voltage quality.
Product standard IEC 60871-1 - Shunt capacitors for a.c. power systems having a rated voltage above 1 000 V – Part 1: General</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
